# ASHWIN BALAKRISHNA

### WEB DEVELOPER



- +91 9791091511
- ashwinbkrish@gmail.com
- **Q** Chennai, India
- linkedin.com/in/ashwin-balakrishna

## PROFILE

A passionate developer with about 2 years of working experience in React Projects. Specialized in working with teams to achieve efficiency goals. With a goal-oriented personality, easily adapts to new technologies. Highly passionate about brainstorming and learning new technologies

## SKILLS

- React Js
- Next Js
- REDUX
- Bootstrap & Tailwind
- EC2 Instances
- GIT
- Leadership
- Communication
- Organisation

# EXPERIENCE

#### **PRODUCT ENGINEER**

Codingmart Technologies - 2HUB 10/2020 - PRESENT

- Responsible for the enhancement and maintenance of the Platform and management system, with Nextjs
- Managed and allocated the frontend team as per designs and new launch requirements.
- Brainstormed solutions for various non technical blockers. .
- Maintain quality and ensure the responsiveness of applications.

## PRODUCT ENGINEER

Codingmart Technologies - KALANJU 04/2020 - 09/2022

- . Responsible for the set-up and maintenance of the content
- Converted the Figma design into working single page web application using Reactjs
- Maintain quality and ensure the responsiveness of applications.
- Integrated API's from third party resources.
- Maintain code integrity and organization.

## EDUCATION

B.E CSE

Rajalakshmi Institute Of Technology

2017-2021